Thank you for watching!
Here you go, it's starting.
It's time for the "Halo! Stay, this time with Miki Nonaka of Morning Musume。 23's Miki Nonaka and
Yuki Hirayama of Angulum.
This time, I'm going to introduce you to the two of them, so please bear with me until the end.
This time, we will be presenting the last "Halo! This is the last "Halo!
Well, another year has come to an end, hasn't it?
Yes, it is.
I think a lot has happened this year,
Yes, I think so.
Did you have any big news?
Yes, I did. This is a very personal story,
I cut off 20 cm of my hair this year,
Yes.
At the beginning of this year, I had bangs,
I had bangs at the beginning of this year, and I think that my hair or my image in terms of appearance was very important in this year.
It looks great on you today.
Thank you very much.
Your impression has really changed dramatically,
Yes, I did.
Both of them were great before,
but the current haircut also has a very mature look,
Thank you very much.
And the big news for Nonaka?
Yes, I have.
On a personal note, I graduated from college.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Yes, that's right. That's right.
I had a lot of work to do,
My thesis project was also related to my work and the program,
I would like to make the most of it in the future.
Yes.
Project Year End Party 2023 Good Bye & Hello!
The 30th will be held in Tokyo, and the 31st will be held simultaneously in Tokyo and Osaka,
That's great.
On the 31st, Morning Musume。 23 will perform in Tokyo and Angelem will perform in Osaka.
It's the end of the year, isn't it?
That's right.
What kind of stage do you want to perform on?
This Year End Party is also the stage where I performed for my debut, so I have a lot of memories from that event.
And also, Morning Musume。 23 changed several times, and the 17th term members joined the group,
I hope you will watch over the new organization.
The day after tomorrow, we will be performing on Countdown Japan 2324.
Morning Musume。's 23 and Angelem will also perform. 23 and Angstrom will both be performing.
Yes, I think so. I am very grateful that Angelem will be decorating the Galaxy Stage with a bird.
Yes, it is. I think the bird is a very important role,
I would like to do my best to create a wonderful stage so that we can be the bird of the day until the very end.
I am looking forward to it.
Morning Musume。 13 will be performing on the Earth Stage,
We are going to perform on the Earth Stage. I will do my best with my physical strength and enthusiasm.
Thank you for your support.
Please take a look at this video.
Here you go!
Yeah!
I want to talk, I want to fall in love
I can't decide which one I want to be in love with
I want to chase one and get three.
I'm greedy.
Wear a bathrobe, tie a cappa together.
Live in bed, zero raps.
Paint all over it. Nothing but natural matches.
Bungy view, runner.
He said he'd see you today. He said it'd be special and cheap.
Wait, wait, wait! Taxi, over there! Pont, overvan!
Don't miss the eye. Hang in there.
Fearless, my mom's super.
Ride your toupee, wear your lipstick
Fearless, fearless, ride your toupee, put on your lips and GO!
This is life, genius overtune
I'm pretty full of life and I'm having a blast.
Oh, yeah. Well, you can't beat the slime.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Instead of assimilating. Who's that? Who?
You're such a hopeless romantic.
That's not even a good idea.
Chokote, Gattening, Gattening.
Gutbutte bar at a live concert
Ah, that's what I'm talking about. I wish I could be like that.
A little jealousy goes a long way.
Yeah, it's a great weapon.
I'm gonna buy her.
No more armor.
I'm gonna stab her and hit her.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's called an age.
Hey, Disk Taker.
Come on, let's be disc takers.
One step on the path of truth.
I can't believe it's too late.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
100 years of life. Traffic is inflating.
Now is the best time
No premonition
Tonton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton, ton.
Not impossible
Let's speak the truth
Our lives are open to rave reviews
Rather reality
Kiss now
It is 100%
I want it to come true
Yeah, yeah.
You can do it.
You want to do it.
That's pride.
Oh, my God!
Any job, any job, any job.
Be me, be me, be me, be me, be me, be me, be me, be me, be me, be me, be me
Love me, Move me, Life is a beautiful
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
I'm sorry if I made you nervous.
Labyrinth of left and right... No.
Your fist
Fulfill your oath
Elevation
In rhythm
One Train
Such a time
I'm free to do what I want
I'm going to dance
in my town
Swimming in the Universe
Searching for meaning
Around the world
Sneaking around is a boo-boo
I don't need time off.
I don't want to be offline. That's a lie.
Egitive video, that's what this is.
Who wants to be offline?
Yes!
My life is good. I'm winning.
I'm pretty content. Sleepy or sad?
Yes, it's a game!
LIFE IS TOO SHORT
I screwed up today. It's okay.
I'd rather be sorry than sorry.
To what end
Love, it's an experience, an experience, a super-experience.
To anyone and everything
All in all LIFE IS TOO SHORT
LIFE IS TOO SHORT
I love the way you're trying so hard.
Morning Musume。' 23's Miki Nonaka and Angulum's Yuki Hirayama present Halo! STE.
I'm going to ask you some questions, so don't think too much and answer them quickly.
Please do. I'll get right to it.
It's been two years since you joined Angulum on the 30th. What is the best word to describe these two years?
Gumshoeing Yuki, whose motto is "continuity is power", what have you continued to do this year? Head massage
Seven months have passed since the junior members joined the group. Feelings
What songs do you particularly enjoy performing? Friends of Angulum And this year, 2023, was the 25th anniversary of Hello Project.
What is one song that you found new and fascinating through the 25th anniversary events and projects? Aa-san's first kiss.
That's all. Thank you for your time. I'd like to dig a little deeper into the answers that caught my attention.
What I was wondering was, what has changed so much in you since the junior members joined the group 7 months ago? I would like to know what you meant by your feelings.
Well, when I was the youngest, I was in a great hurry to do my best, but after the junior members joined, I realized that it's not good to be too impatient.
I understood that it is not good to be too impatient, and I changed my way of thinking about doing my best while having a certain amount of leeway in my mind.
I think I've changed the way I usually do my best, and I'm really mature now.
I don't think that's true. And one song that I found new and fascinating through the 25th anniversary events and projects...
Asami
I was able to see this song live, and it was a very beautiful performance.
I sang this song at my birthday event, and I really liked it to begin with.
But when I saw it live on the monitor in the sleeve, it was so powerful and I just thought it was so beautiful.
Really?
It was so beautiful that I was at a loss for words.
I really love this song, and it made me feel how cool you are.
It was a moment that made me think Hello Project is the best, wasn't it?
Yes, it was great!
Questions for Ms. Nonaka will be asked after the VTR.
Hello! Sta.
Anjelm Red Line
Angulum, Red Line
Halo! Ste.
Next, I would like to ask a question to Ms. Nonaka. Please do.
Yes, you released your second photo book on your 24th birthday. What did you work on for the photo shoot?
Muscle training for my buttocks.
About a month after Ms. Fukumura's graduation, I was asked to write the perfect words for Morning Musume。 What is the best word to describe Morning Musume。
Challenge into everything!
Yes, what do you think you personally accomplished in 2023?
Living in the moment.
What is your favorite subject besides English?
Science.
Project's 25th anniversary. What moment did you feel the history of the project?
Iki-masshoi!
I'm ready to go!
Yes, thank you very much.
Well, I'd like to go on my own and talk about what I like about Morning Musume,
What is the best word for the current Morning Musume。 I'm not very good at English, so I'd love to hear your explanation,
I am not good at English, so please explain it to me.
I said, "Challenge into everything!
It means let's challenge everything.
I hope that each one of us will be able to take on more and more challenges in Japan with greed, since our organization has been changed,
I will use this word.
Challenges are important, aren't they?
I will do my best.
Next, what subjects other than English are you good at?
I personally wanted to know,
Since we are talking about science, do you like to do experiments in science?
I like physics and science,
I see.
I think I am only bad at biology, but yes.
I've always liked physics a lot, and I enjoy it,
I'm glad you asked me this, because I don't get asked this very often.
I was very happy to learn more about you again.
I am happy too.
Yes, I am.
We will continue after this talk.
Next Episode Preview
Episode 1 Idols
Episode 2 Idols
Episode 3 Idols
It's okay to like clothes that are a little more flashy than everyone else's.
It's fine.
It's none of your business if you think you're being bossy behind your back.
You're the one who makes me feel like I'm good enough for you.
But no one can take your place.
I want to believe... this... this... this... this is the new rhythm.
I could have been instinctive if I'd just danced
I was staring at myself more tightly than anyone else.
I'm sure... I'm sure... I'm sure...
Even if it's just a beat and a sideways glance...
I'm still me, after all...
Let's go!
It's fine if we just go our own way, isn't it?
Don't get swept away, but don't be afraid to say "I'll stay afloat".
Feelin' like you're the only one in my life
I know that's not true.
That's right.
This, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this, this...
I'm always in the same mood.
In a sea of people, but it's still wide
Oh yeah, the earth is water
Here, here, here, here, here
I'm not here enough
That's not what I sang
I want to be the earth My heart
I wonder if it's enough to be a star
You can't say "Alota".
I can't take anyone's place.
I'll never be anyone's replacement.
I want to believe
This is it, this is it, this is it, this is the new rhythm
If you dance, you'll get this look in your eyes
It's more than just being me for once
I'll always want to admit it
I'm sure, I'm sure, I'm sure
I'm sure I'm sure I'm sure
You grabbed my hand.
You just wanted to take care of it.
You went through so much hope.
That's how you'll gradually become me.
[Applause]
Thank you for everything. I'm rooting for you, too.
Okay, we've got a couple of questions for you, and we're going to share the answers with you in the sketchbook.
I've already written the mvp for Hello Project 2023 in my sketchbook, so I'd like to share it with you.
The mvp that I, Hirayama, have chosen is Moe Kanbukuro!
Yes, Mr. Kanbukuro, as the leader of the new organization, when we released our first single, you talked a lot with the staff about what kind of songs we wanted to sing, and you gathered a lot of opinions from the members.
She talked a lot with the staff about how they wanted to sing this kind of song, and she put together a lot of opinions from the members to make Angeleum better.
She made a lot of efforts to make Angeleum better, so I chose Ms. Moe Kanbukuro.
In my mind, she is Rio Sakurai, and she is also a teacher for Rio Sakurai, but in my mind, she is really.......
She was in her second year with us, but she was growing very fast and she had great balance and a very high growth rate.
If I could write about any of them, I would write about Haruka Inoue, a member of the 17th term, Tomoko Inoue, and also Haruko Inoue.
I really wanted to write about all the new members who joined JuiceJuice and Angelem.
I really wanted to write about all of them.
Okay, now I'd like to go to the next question. What was the best moment for Morning Musume' 23 Angulum this year?
I wrote "Yokohama Arena" in my mind.
It's still fresh in my mind, but we performed 2days at Yokohama Arena with Morning Musume。 23.
The first day was a collaboration with OG members, and the second day was the graduation of Sei Fukumura, so it was really a very intense 2 days in the year 2023.
It was the first time for me to do a live concert at Yokohama Arena, so it was a fresh and happy experience for me.
Thank you very much. I am at the moment of the announcement of the new organization.
This was the first time for all 12 of us to stand on the stage together.
Then the two new members, Yukiho and Hana Goto, were on the lower board.
Yukiho and Hana Goto came out on stage wearing white costumes.
I think that moment was the best moment of this year for Angulum.
Yes, it was.
So, the last question will come after the VTR.
The presentation of the lyrics that touched my heart
Yay!
In this corner, we will present lyrics from Hello!
Project songs and talk about their charms.
Project's songs and talk about their charms. Project songs and talk about their charms.
I hope you can understand the charm of the song.
So, this week, I, Kanon Kotoi, will present the song.
So here it is.
Belene.
Belene is very rare, isn't it?
Really?
It is very difficult to live straight.
Temptation and timidity whisper to you.
What is it that you love? What is it that you want to do?
Do you even lose sight of what is important? I think.
It's Berryz KOBO's "Ai wa atumo kimi no naka ni" ("Love is always inside of you"),
Each lyric of this song is really like its own.
So I wasn't sure which part to listen to or how much to write here,
But here it is.
As you can see, it is very difficult to live a straight life.
I think that's true,
But there are so many things,
I think that temptation and cowardice are probably just things that make you want to do something bad,
I think that's what it's all about,
I mean, wanting to do bad things,
I don't want to do bad things, or to have only a kind heart,
In life, you may have not only a kind heart, but also a bad heart,
When I have not only a kind heart, but also a bad heart, or when I have a bad heart in my life,
I don't know how to live, and I don't know how to live,
I don't know how to live,
I think that's why I don't know how to live my life or how to express myself,
But then, they start to think about what they want to do and what they really want to do,
I wonder what it would be like not to be able to express what you love, what you want to do, what you really want to do, or what you really think you want to do,
The lyrics make you think, "What if I can't express what I really want to do?
This is what it's like to lose sight of what's important to you.
So, don't lose sight of yourself and what you like to do,
I want a world where I can do what I like, what I want to do, what I want to do, what I think I want to do, without losing sight of myself,
I think the lyrics of the song are about being that kind of person,
It's very deep.
I like this song.
I really like it.
Hanane is in the third grade of junior high school, right?
I think it's amazing that she can feel it so deeply in her third year of middle school.
It is very difficult to live immediately.
So, although I have a past self, I often think that the present is just the present.
I don't think about this person because of the way she was in the past,
I am sure that there are many things that happened to her before she came to her present family and her present life,
I want to see her not only in her bad parts, but also in the way she is now.
I would like to see her as she is now,
Let's look at the good things about all kinds of people!
Yes, sir!
See you next week!
Now that I have answered your questions looking back on the year 2023, here is the last question.
The last one is a message to myself one year from now. Your message to yourself at the end of the year 2024.
I have written this one and would like to present it. Se-no!
Ta-da! What about you, Yuki-chan?
I, Hirayama, answered "Be polite," and I answered "I've been working hard for the past two years,
My goal for this year is to be polite, but I thought I would forget about it after a year, so I wrote this carefully to tell people to be polite again and to do their best.
I always say "be polite," but that's not true. That's not true. I will be instructed by my teacher, so I will do my best to be polite.
I want to do my best and enjoy the moment. Yes, it's important!
In the question-and-answer section, the question was "What have you accomplished this year? In the question-and-answer section, I was asked what I accomplished this year, and I said something about enjoying the present moment,
I think the situation will change from time to time, and I don't know what the situation will be like next year, so I would like to be a person who can really make efforts that suit the moment. I would like to enjoy myself.
You have looked back on 2023, and I am really looking forward to 2024. Yes, I am looking forward to it. I will continue to do my best, and I look forward to working with you. Thank you very much.
Hallo! STE
Morning Musume。 23's Miki Nonaka and Yuki Hirayama of Angeleum will be presenting the "Halo! STE. It is time for us to say goodbye. We would like to announce that on December 30 and 31, we will be holding the Hello! Project Year-End Party 2023Goodbye & Hallo! Project Year-End Party 2023 Goodbye & Hallow!
Project Year-End Party 2023 Goodbye & Hallo! Morning Musume。 23 will perform in Tokyo and Angelem will perform in Osaka.
Project 2024 Winter 3ofusus will be held from January 2 next year. Project 2024 Winter 3 ofus will start on January 2. Morning Musume。 24Tsubaki Factory Beyonce as Team A and Anjelm JuiceJuice Ochanoma as Team B will tour all over Japan.
Angulum's new single Red Line Life is Beautiful is now on sale.
It is the first single since the new formation.
It is a very nice new song and a very targeted song, so please check it out.
And on January 17, Angelem concert 2023 Big Love! BVD and Blu-ray of "From Angulum with love" will be released on January 17.
It will be the first performance as Angulum at Yokohama Arena, and it will also be the graduation performance of Akari Takeuchi, so please check it out.
And on February 7, Morning Musume。 Grad Quarter Century at Nippon Budokan will be released on BVD and Blu-ray on February 7.
This is the 25th anniversary concert of Morning Musume。 This is a concert to commemorate the 25th anniversary of Morning Musume。
The concert will be held at the Hallow! Project members will appear on this channel more and more.
Project members. New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please subscribe to the channel.
This time I will be talking with Miki Nonaka from Morning Musume。 23's Miki Nonaka and Angulum's Yuki Hirayama.
Have a Happy New Year!
Lastly, 24 members including 10 OG members and 14 energetic members of Morning Musume。
Love Machine
I know, it's too good to be true.
I really don't
So party party party
I even say so myself
It's not just a party.
I'm not?
I can't wake up from this.
Lonely Everybody Party Party
No one knows
When will you realize you're in love?
Dynamite
Love is Dynamite
No matter how uncomfortable I am
Honey Bunny, I'm touching you
Like this
I've tried being nice to you
To a brighter future
I'm gonna get a job
Wow, wow, wow, wow
The future of Japan
Wow Wow Wow Wow
The envy of the world
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Let's fall in love
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Dancing all the night
I don't know...
My darling
I want you to love me everywhere
I'll tell her myself.
You're a little embarrassed, aren't you?
We're the perfect couple.
I've always wanted to be Everybody's Party Party
Everyone is unaware of it
Love is a Mystery
Love is a mystery
It's forbidden to fall in love because it's unnatural
But if you're still good at it
I'll be happy one day
I'm waiting for a cancellation
Wow wow wow wow
The smile on your face
The world will envy you
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Talk about having a dream
Wow wow wow wow
Dance, dance, pray All the night
Let's get loud!
Woo!
Hey!
Let's get loud!
Everybody, together.
One more time!
Love Love Machine
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow
Love Love Love Love Station
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Love Love Love Factory
Wow Wow Wow Wow
Love is so wonderful
Hope for the future
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
The world will envy you
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah
Let's fall in love
Wow Wow Wow Wow Dance
Dancing all the night
Even on a bowling bus
Wow Wow Wow Wow
You and me both
Yeah yeah yeah yeah
Everybody's a chacho
Wow Wow Wow Wow Dance
Dancing all the night
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
Thank you for watching!
Love Machine